That a
very good health insurance product of Taliban Star Health Insurance has
come in the market, the instrument
clear insurance policy is
designed for minutes and
for the female child, this product has
many amazing features, like if you have
taken the policy before then you do
not have to subscribe, it can be
very good for play,
soon complete information will be
appointed, let's talk about the basic details, the
subscription is
98100, but if the female child is a
dependent, then you can
subscribe, this policy can be
taken for both individual and family floater, in individual it
is allowed only for email and in family floater
this product can be taken for minute and maximum child
and in this the proposal can be only email,
pregnant women can subscribe by
submitting their scan report, if we
talk about obscure new born baby, then in this product you can subscribe for 5 lakh,
room rent
in this policy is 150 cm and maximum 20, you
can click, it is an ambulance product,
whatever your company gives you  It will be included in the air ambulance,
which is
now
available on the school policy. Free hospitalization
is 60 days and post-hospitalization is in
three days. See, this product
covers hair treatment. AYUSH
treatment, that is, Ayurveda Siddha Unani.
In this product, you can claim up to 10 minutes.
Treatments of yoga and naturopathy will
not be included in this. Organ donors can
plan up to the sum insured in this plan. The
organ donor limit is over and
above the limit, that is, the expenses of the
organ donor will
not be covered in your Someshwar. The
additional 7 minutes can only be
utilized by the donor and not by the policy holder. The
next feature
of this product is Star Mother Care. If a
female child is below 12 years of age and is
admitted to the hospital, then the company
can also provide her a private AC room. If a
room is not available in that hospital, then the
company
can subscribe for a deposit maximum of ₹50, which is the hotel rate.  There is a criteria
here also that the policy holder should be 10
kilometers from the hospital, this
benefit is additional only for help,
which helps by covering separately in the coverage, then the
company will give no claim bonus of
10 minutes more which will be increased up to the maximum, it is
a very amazing feature product
which is for automatic restoration of
accused and full claim and
you can claim up to a maximum of 200, which
you can use for the past and the maximum
liability of the company
is up to 10 minutes once a year and whatever your
balance is, you cannot carry it forward for the next,
modern
treatment is covered in 20 products, if
your sum insured is between 5 lakh to 15 lakh,
then you can claim up to fifty percent at that time and
if your sum insured is
between 5 lakh to 50 lakh, then
you can claim up to 14% of the sum insured
and if your sum insured is one crore, then up
to 30 percent of the sum insured  You
can click on this product's next amazing
feature is miscarriage or accident. If the policy
holder has a miscarriage, the company will refund
Rs.25000 for lump sum between Rs.5 lakh to Rs.15 lakh
and Rs.3000 for lump sum between Rs.20 lakh to Rs.25 lakh
and Rs.40000 for lump sum between Rs.50 lakh to Rs.1 crore
once in lifetime. There is a
waiting period of 2 years in policies above Rs.5 lakh
and waiting period is one year in policies above Rs.15 lakh.
You can also add for mental health in maternity expenses plan
which is a very unique
feature. If your sum insured is Rs.5 then you can add up
to Rs.25000. In case of
injury between Rs.10 lakh to Rs.20 lakh, you can add up to Rs.50 thousand. In case of injury between
Rs.25 lakh to Rs.50 lakh, you
can limit up to Rs.75 thousand
and in case of injury between Rs.1 crore  You can claim up to Rs 1 lakh on sum assured,
which is the maximum amount you
can claim for. The
waiting period is 2 years for Rs 5 lakh and Rs 10 lakh sum assured,
and for
Rs 15 lakh sum assured, there is a waiting period of only one year
for delivery expenses,
which is very less. In
comparison to other products in the market, the
Points Points product can be claimed from
Hospital Express Faizabad
to Ground Shot for the new born baby, that is, the
coverage of the new born baby will be
from the first day and the maximum claim you
can make is 25 percent of the 7-month claim. The
company also claims for the vaccination of the new born baby, which is for a maximum of
one year. There is a limit on 5 lakh
and 10 lakh insurance and there is a limit on other things, from
15 lakh and above, the
maximum limit on the minimum claim is up to ₹35,100.
Preventive health  Checkups
are covered in the product, which we are putting on the screen, you
can check them. For females aged 13 to 19 years,
you can click on the Thousand Rupees Senior cover. The cover is
₹239 for females and ₹300
for senior citizens. If
a male is included in this policy, then the
maximum help cycle you can claim is ₹1000. The
next feature of this product is
Star Balance Program. You
can avail discount up to 10.7% on the premium by turning on your balance points on this page, which are based on
different parameters like your health
risk assessment. Free points. Preventive
risk assessment 210 points. Weight management
program. You can also avail pain treatment
in this policy, which
is available only for weight loss and nutrition, which ranges
from ₹500 to ₹5000 according to the sum insured.
You can click on it. Metabolic
screening is also available in this product.  You
can click on it which is
available for the test of the new born baby in which it is
checked how healthy the new born baby
is, its maximum limit is
Rs.35, there is a feature called depression
consultation which
is available for maximum four consultations and maximum check can be done on one side for 12 years
and its
consultation charges are Rs.510, you
can also claim for pain management in this policy which we are
putting on the screen, you can check it, there are
different limits which can be taken at the end of 5 lakhs, fifty thousand
subscription and
you can also check it in the policy building, the
company also claims the collateral items on this plan, that is,
if you require admission in the hospital, then
whatever
non-collateral items are there as per the company's bill list,
you will get the amount from the non-collateral item,
in the product
you can also claim for side production treatment
which is an
infertility treatment  It is for the delivery of a baby,
whose waiting period is of three years
and we are putting its limit on the screen,
not on the sum insured of 5 lakhs, up
to ₹5000 on 10 lakhs and up to ₹1.5 lakh
on 15 lakhs, up to ₹
2 lakh on 50 lakhs sum insured,
up to 2.5 lakhs on 50 lakhs sum insured and up
to ₹1 lakh per lakh for sum insured near 1 crore, you
can click on this plan, antenatal
care pregnancy care is also covered, which
you can change after pregnancy is confirmed,
₹400 on 5 lakhs to 15 lakhs sum insured
and ₹20 lakhs to 20 crores sum insured,
you can click on this plan, there is a
waiting period of 2 years on sum insured of 5 lakhs to 10 lakhs
and there is a
waiting period of one year on sum insured of 15 to 20 crores, if you
take share room in this plan then ₹2000
birthday plan  You can avail this plan for a maximum of 7 days,
i.e., in case of taking a showroom, you will get
₹2000. The company will offer flat share accommodation benefit.
In this plan, you
can add optional cancer cover. In case of cancer or dengue, the
minimum coverage will be at a lump sum premium. The
company will offer this plan to the policy holder
whose waiting period is as
specified, that is, it is equal and this can be done
on an individual basis and
its limit excluding accessories is between Rs 5 lakh to Rs
25 lakh.
You can avail this plan only once. Once availed, the
optional cover cannot be renewed.
You can avail this plan for one year, two years and three years.
If you
avail this plan for two years together, you get a
temple tax discount. If you avail this plan for three
years, you get a temple tax discount on the second year and a
temple tax discount on the third year. The
company offers a discount of Rs 11.25 lakh on the third year.
You can also avail this plan in installment mode,
which is your quarterly and half-
yearly basis.  It is also available on and the guarantee is
of 7 days. In this policy, if you do
not enroll in your policy on time, then your policy will lapse.
Talking about waiting periods,
you have a waiting period of first three days. Do not
forget that there is a waiting period of two days for any kind of fresh and
specific
diseases like cataract, stone, anklet, Sarnia,
Antichrist Extra.
If you have any disease before taking the policy, then you
can claim it after 2 years, but
for this surgery there is a waiting period of 2 years.
We have already told you about the waiting period for delivery and miscarriage. You
can renew this policy for life long and
whatever premium you pay can be
claimed under section 80G of tax benefit.
If you feel that you have
not selected the right plane, then the free look
period which
is definitely 30 days from distance marketing, you can cancel your plane and
get your money refunded. So
this was the review of
Amazing Women Care of Star Health Insurance.  Like the health insurance
plan. If you
liked the video, we keep bringing such phone information,
so please like and subscribe to our channel.
Thank you for
watching.